// ignore_for_file: file_names

import 'package:ibenture/models/lesson_model.dart';

List<ExamQuestions> examQuestions = [
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'What is the primary purpose of Competitor Analysis?',
    examoptions: ['To understand competitors’ strengths, weaknesses, and strategies', 'To forecast future demand for products', 'To segment the market into distinct sub-groups', 'To analyze overall market trends'],
    examanswer: 'To understand competitors’ strengths, weaknesses, and strategies',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'Which method involves assessing competitors’ strengths and weaknesses?',
    examoptions: ['SWOT Analysis', 'Market Segmentation', 'Demand Forecasting', 'Customer Analysis'],
    examanswer: 'SWOT Analysis',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'What should be analyzed to understand competitors’ market position?',
    examoptions: ['Market Share Data and Positioning Maps', 'Customer Feedback and Reviews', 'Competitors’ Marketing Tactics', 'Product Features and Pricing Strategies'],
    examanswer: 'Market Share Data and Positioning Maps',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'What does Competitive Advantage focus on?',
    examoptions: ['Unique value proposition and differentiation', 'Analyzing market trends and shifts', 'Evaluating competitors’ weaknesses', 'Understanding customer behavior and preferences'],
    examanswer: 'Unique value proposition and differentiation',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'How can a business achieve Competitive Advantage?',
    examoptions: ['By developing a unique value proposition and focusing on innovation', 'By analyzing market trends and shifts', 'By understanding customer feedback and reviews', 'By segmenting the market into distinct sub-groups'],
    examanswer: 'By developing a unique value proposition and focusing on innovation',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'Which aspect of Competitor Analysis involves examining competitors’ marketing campaigns?',
    examoptions: ['Understanding Competitors’ Strategies', 'Analyzing Competitors’ Strengths and Weaknesses', 'Identifying Competitors', 'Assessing Market Position and Share'],
    examanswer: 'Understanding Competitors’ Strategies',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'What is a benefit of analyzing Market Position and Share?',
    examoptions: ['Gaining insights into market dynamics and positioning', 'Understanding competitors’ strategies and tactics', 'Forecasting future demand for products', 'Identifying customer needs and preferences'],
    examanswer: 'Gaining insights into market dynamics and positioning',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'What should businesses focus on to achieve cost leadership?',
    examoptions: ['Reducing costs to offer competitive pricing', 'Developing a unique value proposition', 'Analyzing competitors’ strengths and weaknesses', 'Understanding customer behavior and preferences'],
    examanswer: 'Reducing costs to offer competitive pricing',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'What does a unique value proposition provide in terms of Competitive Advantage?',
    examoptions: ['A distinct edge that sets the business apart from competitors', 'Insights into market trends and shifts', 'Understanding competitors’ weaknesses', 'Customer feedback and reviews'],
    examanswer: 'A distinct edge that sets the business apart from competitors',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'What is the benefit of Competitive Advantage for a business?',
    examoptions: ['Increased market share and higher profit margins', 'Better understanding of customer preferences', 'Forecasting future market demand', 'Analyzing competitors’ strategies'],
    examanswer: 'Increased market share and higher profit margins',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'What is Competitor Identification?',
    examoptions: ['Determining who your main competitors are', 'Analyzing competitors’ marketing campaigns', 'Assessing competitors’ financial performance', 'Understanding market trends'],
    examanswer: 'Determining who your main competitors are',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'Which method helps to identify competitors in the market?',
    examoptions: ['Market Research', 'SWOT Analysis', 'PEST Analysis', 'Business Model Canvas'],
    examanswer: 'Market Research',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'What is SWOT Analysis used for in Competitor Analysis?',
    examoptions: ['Evaluating competitors’ strengths and weaknesses', 'Assessing market trends', 'Understanding customer preferences', 'Identifying opportunities for innovation'],
    examanswer: 'Evaluating competitors’ strengths and weaknesses',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'Which component of SWOT Analysis focuses on external factors that could benefit the business?',
    examoptions: ['Opportunities', 'Strengths', 'Weaknesses', 'Threats'],
    examanswer: 'Opportunities',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'What should be analyzed to understand competitors’ strategies?',
    examoptions: ['Marketing Tactics', 'Customer Feedback', 'Market Share Data', 'Financial Performance'],
    examanswer: 'Marketing Tactics',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'What is a key benefit of Understanding Competitors’ Strategies?',
    examoptions: ['Developing strategies to outperform competitors', 'Identifying customer preferences', 'Analyzing market trends', 'Assessing technological advancements'],
    examanswer: 'Developing strategies to outperform competitors',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'Which analysis focuses on assessing financial performance and market share?',
    examoptions: ['Market Position and Share Analysis', 'Competitor Strengths and Weaknesses Analysis', 'Competitor Strategy Analysis', 'Competitor Identification'],
    examanswer: 'Market Position and Share Analysis',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'What does Market Position and Share Analysis help with?',
    examoptions: ['Gaining insights into market dynamics and positioning', 'Understanding competitors’ strategies', 'Analyzing customer feedback', 'Evaluating financial performance'],
    examanswer: 'Gaining insights into market dynamics and positioning',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'What aspect of Competitive Analysis involves reviewing competitors’ product features and pricing strategies?',
    examoptions: ['Understanding Competitors’ Strategies', 'Analyzing Competitors’ Strengths and Weaknesses', 'Identifying Competitors', 'Assessing Market Position and Share'],
    examanswer: 'Understanding Competitors’ Strategies',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'What does Competitor Strengths and Weaknesses Analysis involve?',
    examoptions: ['Evaluating what competitors do well and where they fall short', 'Understanding market trends', 'Assessing customer preferences', 'Identifying external threats'],
    examanswer: 'Evaluating what competitors do well and where they fall short',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'How can businesses leverage competitors’ weaknesses?',
    examoptions: ['By identifying areas where competitors are lacking', 'By analyzing market trends', 'By understanding customer feedback', 'By reviewing competitors’ financial performance'],
    examanswer: 'By identifying areas where competitors are lacking',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'What does Competitive Advantage focus on achieving?',
    examoptions: ['Higher profit margins and increased market share', 'Better understanding of customer preferences', 'Analyzing competitors’ strategies', 'Identifying market trends'],
    examanswer: 'Higher profit margins and increased market share',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'Which analysis tool is useful for creating positioning maps to visualize competitors’ positions?',
    examoptions: ['Market Position and Share Analysis', 'Competitive Analysis', 'SWOT Analysis', 'PEST Analysis'],
    examanswer: 'Market Position and Share Analysis',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'What is a primary focus of the Competitive Advantage?',
    examoptions: ['Unique Value Proposition', 'Understanding market trends', 'Analyzing customer feedback', 'Reviewing financial performance'],
    examanswer: 'Unique Value Proposition',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'What does Market Share Data help to assess?',
    examoptions: ['Competitors’ position in the market', 'Customer preferences', 'Technological advancements', 'Market trends'],
    examanswer: 'Competitors’ position in the market',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'What is a benefit of analyzing competitors’ marketing tactics?',
    examoptions: ['Identifying innovative approaches', 'Understanding customer feedback', 'Analyzing financial performance', 'Evaluating market trends'],
    examanswer: 'Identifying innovative approaches',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'Which component of SWOT Analysis evaluates the impact of external challenges?',
    examoptions: ['Threats', 'Opportunities', 'Strengths', 'Weaknesses'],
    examanswer: 'Threats',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'What should be included in a Competitive Analysis to gain insights into market dynamics?',
    examoptions: ['Market Position and Share Data', 'Customer Feedback', 'SWOT Analysis', 'PEST Analysis'],
    examanswer: 'Market Position and Share Data',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'What does SWOT Analysis stand for?',
    examoptions: ['Strengths, Weaknesses, Opportunities, Threats', 'Strategic Wins, Opportunities, Threats', 'Systems Weaknesses, Opportunities, Tactics', 'Strengths, Weaknesses, Objectives, Threats'],
    examanswer: 'Strengths, Weaknesses, Opportunities, Threats',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'Which analysis tool focuses on evaluating internal and external factors of a business?',
    examoptions: ['SWOT Analysis', 'PEST Analysis', 'Business Model Canvas', 'Competitive Analysis'],
    examanswer: 'SWOT Analysis',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'What does the Business Model Canvas describe?',
    examoptions: ['Business models and their components', 'Market trends and shifts', 'Competitors’ strategies and tactics', 'Customer feedback and reviews'],
    examanswer: 'Business models and their components',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'What is a key aspect of Competitive Analysis?',
    examoptions: ['Identifying strengths and weaknesses of competitors', 'Analyzing market trends', 'Assessing customer preferences', 'Understanding financial performance'],
    examanswer: 'Identifying strengths and weaknesses of competitors',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'What does the term “Revenue Streams” in the Business Model Canvas refer to?',
    examoptions: ['How the business earns money', 'Key resources needed for operations', 'Major revenue sources', 'Cost structure and expenses'],
    examanswer: 'How the business earns money',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'Which analysis helps in identifying external factors that could benefit the business?',
    examoptions: ['Opportunities in SWOT Analysis', 'PEST Analysis', 'Market Research', 'Competitive Analysis'],
    examanswer: 'Opportunities in SWOT Analysis',
  ),
  ExamQuestions(
    examquestion: 'What should businesses focus on to achieve differentiation?',
    examoptions: ['Developing unique features and value propositions', 'Reducing costs', 'Analyzing competitors’ strategies', 'Understanding market trends'],
    examanswer: 'Developing unique features and value propositions',
  ),
];
